A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1947-1951 FA759
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1948
  - Australia, 1948; 1948/410
    - Australia - Nursing, 1948; 1948/410.C
      - Australia, 1948 (Box 421, Folder 2839)
    - Australia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 1948/410.E
      - Australia, 1948 (Box 421, Folder 2839)
    - Australia - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 1948/410.R
      - Australia, 1948 (Box 421, Folder 2839)
  - Tasmania, 1948; 1948/414
    Tasmania
    - Sydenham Hospital, 1948 (Box 421, Folder 2840)
  - New Zealand, 1948; 1948/418
    - New Zealand, 1948 (Box 421, Folder 2840)
    - New Zealand - Medical Sciences, 1948; 1948/418.A
      - New Zealand, 1948 (Box 421, Folder 2840)
    - New Zealand - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 1948/418.E
      - New Zealand, 1948 (Box 421, Folder 2840)
    - New Zealand - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 1948/418.R
      - New Zealand, 1948 (Box 421, Folder 2840)
  - Caribbean, 1948; 1948/420
    - Caribbean Region - Administration, 1948 (Box 421, Folder 2841)
    - Caribbean Region - Administration, 1948 (Box 421, Folder 2842)
    - Caribbean Region - (A-Z), 1948 (Box 421, Folder 2843)
  - Guyana, 1948; 1948/423
    - Guiana, 1948 (Box 421, Folder 2843)
  - Canada, 1948; 1948/427
    - Canada - Administration, 1948 (Box 421, Folder 2844)
    - Canada - (A-Z), 1948 (Box 422, Folder 2845)
    - Canada - (A-Z), 1948 (Box 422, Folder 2846)
    - Canada - Medical Sciences, 1948; 1948/427.A
      - Canada, 1948 (Box 422, Folder 2847)
    - Canada - Nursing, 1948; 1948/427.C
      - Canada, 1948 (Box 422, Folder 2847)
    - Canada - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 1948/427.E
      - Canada, 1948 (Box 422, Folder 2847)
    - Canada - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 1948/427.R
      - Canada, 1948 (Box 422, Folder 2848)
  - Jamaica, 1948; 1948/437
    Jamaica
    - Jamaica, 1948 (Box 422, Folder 2849)
  - Trinidad, 1948; 1948/451
    Trinidad and Tobago
    - Trinidad, 1948 (Box 422, Folder 2849)
  - Grenada, 1948; 1948/455
    Grenada
    - Grenada, 1948 (Box 422, Folder 2849)
  - India, 1948; 1948/464
    - India - General Administration - (A-D), 1948 (Box 422, Folder 2850)
    - India - (E-Z), 1948 (Box 422, Folder 2851)
    - India - Medical Sciences, 1948; 1948/464.A
      - India, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2852)
    - India - Nursing, 1948; 1948/464.C
      - India, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2852)
    - India - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 1948/464.E
      - India, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2852)
    - India - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 1948/464.R
      - India, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2852)
    - India - Social Sciences, 1948; 1948/464.S
      - India, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2852)
  - Pakistan, 1948; 1948/465
    - Pakistan, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2853)
    - Pakistan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 1948/465.E
      - Pakistan, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2853)
    - Pakistan - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 1948/465.R
      - Pakistan, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2853)
  - Burma, 1948; 1948/468
    - Burma, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2853)
    - Burma - Medical Sciences, 1948; 1948/468.A
      - Burma, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2853)
    - Burma - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 1948/468.R
      - Burma, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2853)
  - Iraq, 1948; 1948/470
    - Iraq, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2853)
  - Singapore, 1948; 1948/473
    Singapore
    - Singapore, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2853)
  - Africa, 1948; 1948/475
    - Africa, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2853)
    - Africa - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 1948/475.R
      - Africa, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2853)
  - Kenya, 1948; 1948/476
    Kenya
    - East Africa, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2853)
  - Ethiopia, 1948; 1948/477
    - Ethiopia, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2853)
  - Rhodesia, 1948; 1948/483
    Zimbabwe
    - Zimbabwe - Rhodesia, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2853)
  - Egypt, 1948; 1948/485
    - Egypt - Administration, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2854)
    - Egypt - (A-Z), 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2855)
    - Egypt - Nursing, 1948; 1948/485.C
      - Egypt, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2856)
    - Egypt - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 1948/485.E
      - Egypt, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2856)
  - South Africa, 1948; 1948/487
    - South Africa, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2857)
    - South Africa - Medical Sciences, 1948; 1948/487.A
      - South Africa, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2857)
    - South Africa - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 1948/487.E
      - South Africa, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2857)
    - South Africa - Yellow Fever, 1948; 1948/487.O
      - South Africa, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2857)
  - Zaire, 1948; 1948/495
    Zaire
    - Zaire, 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2857)
  - France, 1948; 1948/500
    - France - (A-G), 1948 (Box 423, Folder 2858)
    - France - (H-N), 1948 (Box 424, Folder 2859)
    - France - (O-Z), 1948 (Box 424, Folder 2860)
    - France - Medical Sciences, 1948; 1948/500.A
      - France, 1948 (Box 424, Folder 2861)
    - France - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 1948/500.E
      - France, 1948 (Box 424, Folder 2861)
    - France - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 1948/500.R
      - France, 1948 (Box 424, Folder 2861)
    - France - Social Sciences, 1948; 1948/500.S
      - France, 1948 (Box 424, Folder 2861)
  - French West Africa, 1948; 1948/521
    French West Africa
    - French Africa, 1948 (Box 424, Folder 2862)
  - Asia, 1948; 1948/600
    - Asia, 1948 (Box 424, Folder 2862)
    - Asia - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 1948/600.R
      - Asia, 1948 (Box 424, Folder 2862)
  - China, 1948; 1948/601
    - China - Administration, 1948 (Box 424, Folder 2863)
    - China - Administration, 1948 (Box 424, Folder 2864)
    - China - (A-P), 1948 (Box 425, Folder 2865)
    - China - (A-P), 1948 (Box 425, Folder 2866)
    - China - (S-Z), 1948 (Box 425, Folder 2867)
    - China - Medical Sciences, 1948; 1948/601.A
      Beijing, China
      - China, 1948 (Box 425, Folder 2868)
    - China - Nursing, 1948; 1948/601.C
      - China, 1948 (Box 425, Folder 2868)
    - China - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 1948/601.E
      - China, 1948 (Box 425, Folder 2868)
    - China - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 1948/601.R
      - China, 1948 (Box 425, Folder 2868)
    - China - Social Sciences, 1948; 1948/601.S
      - China, 1948 (Box 425, Folder 2868)
  - Taiwan, 1948; 1948/605
    Taiwan
    - Taiwan - Medical Sciences, 1948; 1948/605.A
      - Taiwan, 1948 (Box 425, Folder 2869)
    - Taiwan - Nursing, 1948; 1948/605.C
      - Taiwan, 1948 (Box 425, Folder 2869)
    - Taiwan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 1948/605.E
      - Taiwan, 1948 (Box 425, Folder 2869)
  - Japan, 1948; 1948/609
    - Japan - (General) - (A-I), 1948 (Box 425, Folder 2870)
    - Japan - (J-N), 1948 (Box 425, Folder 2871)
    - Japan - (O-Z), 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2872)
    - Japan - Medical Sciences, 1948; 1948/609.A
      - Japan, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2872)
    - Japan - Nursing, 1948; 1948/609.C
      - Japan, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2872)
    - Japan - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1948; 1948/609.D
      - Japan, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2872)
    - Japan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 1948/609.E
      - Japan - (O-Z), 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2872)
      - Japan, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2872)
    - Japan - Social Sciences, 1948; 1948/609.S
      - Japan, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2872)
      - Japan, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2872)
  - Korea, 1948; 1948/613
    - Korea, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2873)
    - Korea - Medical Sciences, 1948; 1948/613.A
      - Korea, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2873)
    - Korea - Nursing, 1948; 1948/613.C
      - Korea, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2873)
    - Korea - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 1948/613.R
      - Korea, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2873)
  - Thailand, 1948; 1948/617
    - Thailand, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2873)
  - Holland, 1948; 1948/650
    - Holland - (A-T), 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2874)
    - Holland - (U-Z), 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2875)
    - Holland - Medical Sciences, 1948; 1948/650.A
      - Holland - (U-Z), 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2875)
    - Holland - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1948; 1948/650.D
      - Holland, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2875)
    - Holland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 1948/650.E
      - Holland, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2875)
    - Holland - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 1948/650.R
      - Holland, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2875)
  - Indonesia, 1948; 1948/652
    - Indonesia, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2876)
    - Indonesia - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 1948/652.R
      - Indonesia, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2876)
  - Pontianak, 1948; 1948/653
    Pontianak (Indonesia)
    - Pontianak, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2876)
  - Dutch East Indies, 1948; 1948/654
    - Dutch East Indies, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2876)
  - Java, 1948; 1948/655
    - Java, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2876)
  - Europe, 1948; 1948/700
    - Europe - Rehabilitation Programs, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2877)
    - Europe - (A-Z), 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2878)
    - Europe - Social Sciences, 1948; 1948/700.S
      - Europe, 1948 (Box 426, Folder 2878)
  - Afghanistan, 1948; 1948/703
    - Afghanistan - Malaria, 1948; 1948/703.I
      - Afghanistan, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2879)
  - Albania, 1948; 1948/704
    Albania
    - Albania, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2879)
  - Austria, 1948; 1948/705
    - Austria, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2879)
    - Austria - (A-Z), 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2880)
    - Austria - Medical Sciences, 1948; 1948/705.A
      - Austria, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2880)
    - Austria - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 1948/705.E
      - Austria, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2880)
    - Austria - Tuberculosis, 1948; 1948/705.T
      - Austria, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2880)
  - Belgium, 1948; 1948/707
    - Belgium, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2881)
    - Belgium - Medical Sciences, 1948; 1948/707.A
      - Belgium, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2881)
    - Belgium - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 1948/707.E
      - Belgium, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2881)
    - Belgium - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 1948/707.R
      - Belgium, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2881)
  - Zaire, 1948; 1948/709
    - Zaire, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2882)
  - Yugoslavia, 1948; 1948/710
    - Yugoslavia, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2882)
    - Yugoslavia - Medical Sciences, 1948; 1948/710.A
      - Yugoslavia, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2882)
    - Yugoslavia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1948; 1948/710.D
      - Yugoslavia, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2882)
  - Bulgaria, 1948; 1948/711
    - Bulgaria, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2882)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1948; 1948/712
    - Czechoslovakia, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2882)
    - Czechoslovakia - Medical Sciences, 1948; 1948/712.A
      - Czechoslovakia, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2883)
    - Czechoslovakia - Nursing, 1948; 1948/712.C
      - Czechoslovakia, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2883)
    - Czechoslovakia - Nursing, 1948; 1948/712.C
      - Czechoslovakia, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2883)
    - Czechoslovakia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 1948/712.E
      - Czechoslovakia, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2883)
  - Denmark, 1948; 1948/713
    - Denmark, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2883)
    - Denmark - Medical Sciences, 1948; 1948/713.A
      - Denmark, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2883)
    - Denmark - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1948; 1948/713.D
      - Denmark, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2883)
    - Denmark - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 1948/713.E
      - Denmark, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2883)
    - Denmark - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 1948/713.R
      - Denmark, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2883)
  - Scandinavia, 1948; 1948/716
    Scandinavia
    - Scandinavia, 1948 (Box 427, Folder 2883)
  - Germany, 1948; 1948/717
    - Germany - (A-Z), 1948 (Box 428, Folder 2884)
    - Germany - (A-Z), 1948 (Box 428, Folder 2885)
    - Germany - (A-Z), 1948 (Box 428, Folder 2886)
    - Germany - Medical Sciences, 1948; 1948/717.A
      - Germany, 1948 (Box 428, Folder 2887)
    - Germany - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1948; 1948/717.D
      - Germany, 1948 (Box 428, Folder 2887)
    - Germany - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 1948/717.E
      - Germany, 1948 (Box 428, Folder 2888)
    - Germany - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 1948/717.R
      - Germany, 1948 (Box 428, Folder 2888)
    - Germany - Social Sciences, 1948; 1948/717.S
      - Germany, 1948 (Box 428, Folder 2888)
  - Greece, 1948; 1948/749
    - Greece, 1948 (Box 429, Folder 2889)
    - Greece - Malaria, 1948; 1948/749.I
      - Greece, 1948 (Box 429, Folder 2889)
  - Hungary, 1948; 1948/750
    - Hungary, 1948 (Box 429, Folder 2889)
    - Hungary - (A-Z), 1948 (Box 429, Folder 2890)
    - Hungary - Medical Sciences, 1948; 1948/750.A
      - Hungary, 1948 (Box 429, Folder 2891)
    - Hungary - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 1948/750.E
      - Hungary, 1948 (Box 429, Folder 2891)
    - Hungary - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 1948/750.R
      - Hungary, 1948 (Box 429, Folder 2891)
  - Italy, 1948; 1948/751
    - Italy - (A-R), 1948 (Box 429, Folder 2892)
    - Italy - (S-Z), 1948 (Box 429, Folder 2893)
    - Italy - Medical Sciences, 1948; 1948/751.A
      - Italy - (S-Z), 1948 (Box 429, Folder 2893)
    - Italy - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 1948/751.E
      - Italy - (S-Z), 1948 (Box 429, Folder 2893)
    - Italy - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 1948/751.R
      - Italy - (S-Z), 1948 (Box 429, Folder 2893)
    - Italy - Social Sciences, 1948; 1948/751.S
      - Italy - (S-Z), 1948 (Box 429, Folder 2893)
  - Luxembourg, 1948; 1948/760
    Luxembourg
    - Luxembourg, 1948 (Box 429, Folder 2894)
  - Norway, 1948; 1948/767
    - Norway, 1948 (Box 429, Folder 2894)
    - Norway - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 1948/767.E
      - Norway, 1948 (Box 429, Folder 2894)
    - Norway - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 1948/767.R
      - Norway, 1948 (Box 429, Folder 2894)
  - Iran, 1948; 1948/771
    - Iran, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2895)
    - Iran - Nursing, 1948; 1948/771.C
      - Iran, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2896)
    - Iran - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 1948/771.E
      - Iran, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2896)
    - Iran - Malaria, 1948; 1948/771.I
      - Iran, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2896)
    - Iran - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 1948/771.R
      - Iran, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2896)
  - Portugal, 1948; 1948/773
    - Portugal, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2897)
    - Portugal - Nursing, 1948; 1948/773.C
      - Portugal, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2897)
    - Portugal - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1948; 1948/773.D
      - Portugal, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2897)
    - Portugal - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 1948/773.E
      - Portugal, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2897)
    - Portugal - Malaria, 1948; 1948/773.I
      - Portugal, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2897)
  - Romania, 1948; 1948/783
    - Romania, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2897)
  - Ukraine, 1948; 1948/784
    - Ukraine - Medical Sciences, 1948; 1948/784.A
      - Ukraine, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2897)
  - USSR, 1948; 1948/785
    - USSR, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2897)
    - USSR - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1948; 1948/785.D
      - USSR, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2897)
    - USSR - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 1948/785.R
      - USSR, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2897)
    - USSR - Social Sciences, 1948; 1948/785.S
      - USSR, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2897)
  - Latvia, 1948; 1948/786
    - Latvia, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2897)
  - Finland, 1948; 1948/787
    - Finland, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2898)
    - Finland - Medical Sciences, 1948; 1948/787.A
      - Finland, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2898)
    - Finland - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1948; 1948/787.D
      - Finland, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2898)
    - Finland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 1948/787.E
      - Finland, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2898)
  - Poland, 1948; 1948/789
    - Poland, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2898)
    - Poland - Medical Sciences, 1948; 1948/789.A
      - Poland, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2898)
    - Poland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 1948/789.E
      - Poland, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2898)
    - Poland - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 1948/789.R
      - Poland, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2898)
  - Spain, 1948; 1948/795
    - Spain, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2899)
  - Sweden, 1948; 1948/800
    - Sweden, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2899)
    - Sweden - Medical Sciences, 1948; 1948/800.A
      - Sweden, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2899)
    - Sweden - Nursing, 1948; 1948/800.C
      - Sweden, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2899)
    - Sweden - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1948; 1948/800.D
      - Sweden, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2899)
    - Sweden - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 1948/800.E
      - Sweden, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2899)
    - Sweden - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 1948/800.R
      - Sweden, 1948 (Box 430, Folder 2899)
  - Liechtenstein, 1948; 1948/802
    liechtenstein
    - Liechtenstein - Malaria, 1948; 1948/802.I
      - Liechtenstein, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2900)
  - Switzerland, 1948; 1948/803
    - Switzerland, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2900)
    - Switzerland - Medical Sciences, 1948; 1948/803.A
      - Switzerland, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2900)
    - Switzerland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 1948/803.E
      - Switzerland, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2900)
    - Switzerland - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 1948/803.R
      - Switzerland, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2900)
  - Near East Region, 1948; 1948/804
    - Near East Region - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 1948/804.R
      - Middle East, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2901)
      - MAR-1 Marshall, John "Middle East Trip", 1948 (Box 563, Folder 3837)
  - Turkey, 1948; 1948/805
    - Turkey, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2901)
    - Turkey - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 1948/805.E
      - Turkey, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2901)
    - Turkey - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 1948/805.R
      - Turkey, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2901)
    - Turkey - Social Sciences, 1948; 1948/805.S
      - Turkey, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2901)
  - Crete, 1948; 1948/807
    Crete
    - Crete, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2901)
  - Cyprus, 1948; 1948/809
    - Cyprus, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2901)
  - Saudi Arabia and Oman, 1948; 1948/817
    Saudi Arabia; Oman
    - Saudi Arabia, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2901)
  - Israel, 1948; 1948/825
    - Israel, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2902)
    - Israel - Medical Sciences, 1948; 1948/825.A
      - Israel, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2902)
  - Lebanon, 1948; 1948/833
    - Syria/Lebanon, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2902)
    - Lebanon - Nursing, 1948; 1948/833.C
      - Syria/Lebanon, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2902)
    - Lebanon - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 1948/833.R
      - Syria/Lebanon, 1948 (Box 431, Folder 2902)
- General Correspondence, 1949
  - International, 1949; 1949/100
    - Staff - International - Aitken, Thomas H., 1949 (Box 431, Folder 2903)
    - Staff - International - Anderson, Richard K., 1949 (Box 431, Folder 2904)
    - Staff - International - Balfour, M. C., 1949 (Box 431, Folder 2905)
    - Staff - International - Bates, Marston, 1949 (Box 431, Folder 2906)
    - Staff - International - Belknap, Chauncey - Bevier, George, 1949 (Box 432, Folder 2907)
    - Staff - International - Buchanan, Norman S. - Bugher, John C. - Burden, Robert P., 1949 (Box 432, Folder 2908)
    - Staff - International - Carr, Henry P., 1949 (Box 432, Folder 2909)
    - Staff - International - Carter, J. C. - Causey, O. R., 1949 (Box 432, Folder 2910)
    - Staff - International - Classification of Knowledge - (Articles), 1949 (Box 432, Folder 2911)
    - Staff - International - Copley, Cecil G. - Crowell, F. Elisabeth - Debevoise, Thomas M. - Diplomatic Service, 1949 (Box 432, Folder 2912)
    - Staff - International - Dyer, Brian R., 1949 (Box 433, Folder 2913)
    - Staff - International - Elmendorf, John E., 1949 (Box 433, Folder 2914)
    - Staff - International - Fahs, Charles B. - Fox, John P., 1949 (Box 433, Folder 2915)
    - Staff - International - Grant, John B. - Gregg, Alan, 1949 (Box 433, Folder 2916)
    - Staff - International - Hackett, Lewis W., 1949 (Box 433, Folder 2917)
    - Staff - International - Hackett, Lewis W., 1949 (Box 433, Folder 2918)
    - Staff - International - Hahn, Richard G., 1949 (Box 434, Folder 2919)
    - Staff - International - Hayes, Guy S., 1949 (Box 434, Folder 2920)
    - Staff - International - Hill, Rolla B. - Hirst, Esther Mary - Hughes, Thomas P., 1949 (Box 434, Folder 2921)
    - Staff - International - Information Exchange - Institute of Current World Affairs, 1949 (Box 434, Folder 2922)
    - Staff - International - International - (A-Z), 1949 (Box 434, Folder 2923)
    - Staff - International - Janney, John H., 1949 (Box 434, Folder 2924)
    - Staff - International - Kendrick, John F. - Kerr, J. Austin - Kimball, Lindsley F., 1949 (Box 435, Folder 2925)
    - Staff - International - Kitchen, Stuart F., 1949 (Box 435, Folder 2926)
    - Staff - International - Lambert, Robert A., 1949 (Box 435, Folder 2927)
    - Staff - International - Leach, Charles L., 1949 (Box 435, Folder 2928)
    - Staff - International - Logan, John A., 1949 (Box 435, Folder 2929)
    - Staff - International - McCoy, O. R., 1949 (Box 435, Folder 2930)
    - Staff - International - Magoon, Estus H. - Mailing Lists, 1949 (Box 435, Folder 2931)
    - Staff - International - Maier, John, 1949 (Box 435, Folder 2932)
    - Staff - International - Marshall, John - Milam, D. Frank, 1949 (Box 436, Folder 2933)
    - Staff - International - Miller, Harry M. - Morison, Robert S., 1949 (Box 436, Folder 2934)
    - Staff - International - Noll, Anna Mary - Oliver, Wale, 1949 (Box 436, Folder 2935)
    - Staff - International - Pan-American Institute of Geography and History, 1949 (Box 436, Folder 2936)
    - Staff - International - Paul, J. Harland, 1949 (Box 436, Folder 2937)
    - Staff - International - Payne, George C. - Peterson, Osler L., 1949 (Box 436, Folder 2938)
    - Staff - International - Pomerat, Gerard R. - Rhind, Flora M. - Rickard, E. R. - Russell, Paul F., 1949 (Box 436, Folder 2939)
    - Staff - International - Sasse, Bruce E. - Smith, H. H. - Smithburn, Kenneth, 1949 (Box 437, Folder 2940)
    - Staff - International - Stevens, David H., 1949 (Box 437, Folder 2941)
    - Staff - International - Strode, George K., 1949 (Box 437, Folder 2942)
    - Staff - International - Taylor, R. M., 1949 (Box 437, Folder 2943)
    - Staff - International - Tennant, Mary Elizabeth, 1949 (Box 437, Folder 2944)
    - Staff - International - Tennant, Mary Elizabeth, 1949 (Box 437, Folder 2945)
    - Staff - International - United Nations - A-Z, 1949 (Box 437, Folder 2946)
    - Staff - International - UNESCO - Fellowships, 1949 (Box 438, Folder 2948)
    - Staff - International - UNESCO, 1949 (Box 438, Folder 2947)
    - Staff - International - UNESCO - Philosophy and Humanities, 1949 (Box 438, Folder 2949)
    - Staff - International - UNESCO - (A-N), 1949 (Box 438, Folder 2950)
    - Staff - International - UNESCO - (O-Z), 1949 (Box 438, Folder 2951)
    - Staff - International - United Nations - W. H. O. - (A-Z), 1949 (Box 438, Folder 2952)
    - Staff - International - Varley, Margaret L., 1949 (Box 439, Folder 2953)
    - Staff - International - Warren, Andrew J., 1949 (Box 439, Folder 2954)
    - Staff - International - Watson, Robert B. - 1-3, 1949 (Box 439, Folder 2955)
    - Staff - International - Watson, Robert B. - 1-3, 1949 (Box 439, Folder 2956)
    - Staff - International - Watson, Robert B. - 1-3, 1949 (Box 439, Folder 2957)
    - Staff - International - Weir, John M. - 1-2, 1949 (Box 439, Folder 2958)
    - Staff - International - Weir, John M. - 1-2, 1949 (Box 439, Folder 2959)
    - Staff - International - Wells, C. W., 1949 (Box 440, Folder 2960)
    - Staff - International - Willits, Joseph H., 1949 (Box 440, Folder 2961)